<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; ABC Vancouver</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>for A Better City</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 17:29:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/ABC-Logo_Full-Colour-No-Van.svg</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; ABC Vancouver</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>ABC Vancouver Statement: Christopher Richardson</title>
		<link>/abc-vancouver-statement-christopher-richardson/</link>
					<comments>/abc-vancouver-statement-christopher-richardson/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Taylor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 17:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE September 25, 2022 VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver released the following statement regarding the candidacy of School Board Trustee candidate Christopher Richardson: “Late Friday afternoon ABC Vancouver was made aware that a charitable organization that Christopher Richardson was a board member of had its charitable status revoked by the Canada Revenue Agency on [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE</p>



<p>September 25, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver released the following statement regarding the candidacy of School Board Trustee candidate Christopher Richardson:</p>



<p>“Late Friday afternoon ABC Vancouver was made aware that a charitable organization that Christopher Richardson was a board member of had its charitable status revoked by the Canada Revenue Agency on September 10th.</p>



<p>“On Saturday, ABC conducted several queries. At the conclusion, ABC sent an email at 8pm Saturday evening to the Chief Election Officer that ABC’s endorsement of Christopher Richardson be removed, knowing that the deadline to do so may have passed.</p>



<p>“Should Mr. Richardson be elected, he would not be able to join the ABC Caucus until the matter is resolved to satisfaction.”</p>



<p>-30-</p>



<p>Media Contact:<br>Kareem Allam<br>604-351-1536</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/abc-vancouver-statement-christopher-richardson/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ABC Vancouver commits to building Vancouver’s first sensory playground</title>
		<link>/abc-vancouver-commits-to-building-vancouvers-first-sensory-playground/</link>
					<comments>/abc-vancouver-commits-to-building-vancouvers-first-sensory-playground/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Team Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 16:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9074</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE September 23, 2022 VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC Majority on Park Board would build Vancouver’s first accessible sensory playground. “Vancouver’s first sensory playground will be a big step towards making our parks more accessible,” said ABC Park Board candidate Jas Virdi. “Children of all abilities deserve to have [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE</p>



<p>September 23, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC Majority on Park Board would build Vancouver’s first accessible sensory playground.</p>



<p>“Vancouver’s first sensory playground will be a big step towards making our parks more accessible,” said ABC Park Board candidate Jas Virdi. “Children of all abilities deserve to have fun.”</p>



<p>Sensory playgrounds are designed to make features more usable and accessible for neurodiverse children and children with mobility challenges. Seattle has built seven sensory playgrounds which have been met with positive feedback.</p>



<p>“These spaces make it easier for children with mobility challenges or children who experience sensory overload to have fun at the playground,” continued Virdi. “This new initiative is about creating a safe, inclusive, and welcoming environment for children of all abilities.”</p>



<p>The proposal builds on ABC’s commitment to make Vancouver the most accessible City in the world, ensuring Vancouver meets the needs of those with developmental disabilities and physical mobility challenges. Other components of ABC’s accessibility plan include supporting job carving initiatives, expanding curb cuts, providing better-individualized learning in schools, and building more supportive housing for those living with developmental disabilities or physical mobility challenges.</p>



<p>“ABC is fully committed to making Vancouver the most accessible city in the world,” concluded Christopher Richardson, ABC School Board candidate and former Vancouver School Board Chair. “ABC majorities on Council, Park Board, and School Board will deliver a safer, more accessible Vancouver.”</p>



<p><br>ABC is the only party running to win majorities on Council, Park Board, and School Board.</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver has nominated nineteen candidates for the October 15th municipal elections; Ken Sim for Mayor; Lenny Zhou, Peter Meiszner, Brian Montague, Mike Klassen, and incumbent City Councillors Rebecca Bligh, Lisa Dominato, and Sarah Kirby-Yung for Council; Brennan Bastyovanszky, Laura Christensen, Angela Haer, Marie-Claire Howard, Scott Jensen, and Jas Virdi for Park Board; Alfred Chien, Preeti Faridkot, Victoria Jung, Christopher Richardson, and Josh Zhang for School Board.</p>



<p>-30-</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong></p>



<p>Taylor Verrall604-968-3067 | <a href="mailto:taylor@abcvancouver.ca">taylor@abcvancouver.ca</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/abc-vancouver-commits-to-building-vancouvers-first-sensory-playground/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ABC Vancouver to fast-track business licensing in the City of Vancouver</title>
		<link>/abc-vancouver-to-fast-track-business-licensing-in-the-city-of-vancouver/</link>
					<comments>/abc-vancouver-to-fast-track-business-licensing-in-the-city-of-vancouver/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Team Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 16:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9071</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE September 22, 2022 VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC Majority on Council would reduce business license wait times from 8.2 months to an absolute maximum of three weeks. “Small businesses are the backbone of Vancouver’s economy,” said ABC Council candidate Lenny Zhou. “We want to ensure that Vancouver is [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE</p>



<p>September 22, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC Majority on Council would reduce business license wait times from 8.2 months to an absolute maximum of three weeks.</p>



<p>“Small businesses are the backbone of Vancouver’s economy,” said ABC Council candidate Lenny Zhou. “We want to ensure that Vancouver is a place where businesses can thrive and create good paying jobs.”</p>



<p>The ABC plan would explore best practices to reduce existing license wait times.</p>



<p>“The City of Vancouver’s business license wait times are among the worst in the region, that’s completely unacceptable,” continued Zhou. “Nobody should have to wait over half a year just to be able to open their business.”</p>



<p>Excessive wait times for business licensing can cause significant negative consequences on local communities and the ability to access neighbourhood services and amenities.</p>



<p>“A strong local economy benefits everyone,” concluded Zhou. “Businesses, workers, and residents alike will benefit from this policy shift.”</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver has nominated nineteen candidates for the October 15th municipal elections; Ken Sim for Mayor; Lenny Zhou, Peter Meiszner, Brian Montague, Mike Klassen, and incumbent City Councillors Rebecca Bligh, Lisa Dominato, and Sarah Kirby-Yung for Council; Brennan Bastyovanszky, Laura Christensen, Angela Haer, Marie-Claire Howard, Scott Jensen, and Jas Virdi for Park Board; Alfred Chien, Preeti Faridkot, Victoria Jung, Christopher Richardson, and Josh Zhang for School Board.</p>



<p>-30-</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong></p>



<p>Taylor Verrall<br>604-968-3067 | <a href="mailto:taylor@abcvancouver.ca">taylor@abcvancouver.ca</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/abc-vancouver-to-fast-track-business-licensing-in-the-city-of-vancouver/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ken Sim criticizes lacklustre public safety proposals from Stewart, Hardwick</title>
		<link>/ken-sim-criticizes-lacklustre-public-safety-proposals-from-stewart-hardwick/</link>
					<comments>/ken-sim-criticizes-lacklustre-public-safety-proposals-from-stewart-hardwick/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Team Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9066</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE September 21, 2022 VANCOUVER — In response to announcements regarding public safety and mental health from two other mayoral candidates ABC Vancouver released the following statement: “Yesterday Mayor Kennedy Stewart announced plans to hire 25 counsellors and TEAM announced their plan to hire one commissioner for the Downtown Eastside to conduct an [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE</p>



<p>September 21, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — In response to announcements regarding public safety and mental health from two other mayoral candidates ABC Vancouver released the following statement:</p>



<p>“Yesterday Mayor Kennedy Stewart announced plans to hire 25 counsellors and TEAM announced their plan to hire one commissioner for the Downtown Eastside to conduct an audit.</p>



<p>“It doesn’t appear to me that the other parties understand the scope of the problem in front of us.</p>



<p>“The ABC plan announced on August 15<sup>th</sup> that would result in the hiring of 100 new police officers and 100 new mental health nurses to enhance the Car 87/88 program and other VPD/Health authority partnered programs.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“Additionally, our plan will implement the usage of peer assisted care teams, establish a low barrier 24-hour recovery centre, shift the City’s social and supportive housing strategy to prioritize the quality of housing, increase the City of Vancouver’s social and supportive housing investments in line with the consumer price index every year, pilot housing to support youth and youth ageing out of care, and call for a region-wide mental health summit to work towards the establishment of a new mental health centre of excellence.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“Vancouverites now have a clear choice on public safety and wellness between the main candidates in this race — the ABC approach that will address both the short and long-term challenges or the approaches of candidates who don’t seem to realize that a problem exists.</p>



<p>“The Mayor’s plan to hire 25 counsellors is woefully inadequate, representing only a drop in the bucket of what is needed and ignores the advice of the Vancouver Police Department and the City’s own data.</p>



<p>“Additionally, the Mayor’s proposal to divert crisis calls away from 911 goes against guidance from both the BC Ministry of Mental Health and will only result in service duplication and slower response times.</p>



<p>“Staff at ECOMM are fully trained and have all the resources required to assess and determine an appropriate response to someone in crisis. They have the ability to directly connect those at risk with the Crisis Centre, Kids Help Phone, Youth in BC Chat, and Health Link. 911 staff at ECOMM have the ability to immediately determine the appropriate response from Fire, Health, or Paramedics and protocols to address less immediate dangers.&nbsp;“If you see someone in crisis please immediately call 911&nbsp; as recommended and advised by the BC Ministry of Mental Health and Addictions (<a href="https://www2.gov.bc.ca/gov/content/governments/organizational-structure/ministries-organizations/ministries/mental-health-addictions#:~:text=Call%209%2D1%2D1%20for,B.C.%20Chat%2C%20and%20Health%20Link">Source</a>)”</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">-30-</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong></p>



<p>Taylor Verrall</p>



<p>604-968-3067 | <a href="mailto:taylor@abcvancouver.ca">taylor@abcvancouver.ca<br><br></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/ken-sim-criticizes-lacklustre-public-safety-proposals-from-stewart-hardwick/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ABC Vancouver hits two substantial campaign milestones</title>
		<link>/abc-vancouver-hits-two-substantial-campaign-milestones/</link>
					<comments>/abc-vancouver-hits-two-substantial-campaign-milestones/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Team Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE September 21, 2022 VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that the campaign had knocked on its 50,000th door in addition to having already made over 100,000 phone calls to Vancouver voters. “ABC Vancouver is excited to announce that we have knocked on our 50,000th door,” said ABC Council candidate Lisa Dominato. “For [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE</p>



<p>September 21, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that the campaign had knocked on its 50,000th door in addition to having already made over 100,000 phone calls to Vancouver voters.<br></p>



<p>“ABC Vancouver is excited to announce that we have knocked on our 50,000th door,” said ABC Council candidate Lisa Dominato. “For months now, our team of candidates and supporters have been door-knocking and making phone calls every single day.”</p>



<p>In addition to knocking on 50,000 doors, ABC also crossed the threshold of making 100,000 phone calls to voters earlier this week.</p>



<p>We’re proud of the response our team has been getting while connecting with residents,” continued Dominato. “Voters across our city want to bring change to Vancouver — they’re ready to see a return of leadership to City Hall, and they’re ready to see meaningful action on community safety, housing, affordability and quality services that make the city more liveable. We have also been hearing concerns around the plans to bring in a road tax.”</p>



<p>Dominato indicated that ABC Vancouver has no plans of slowing down their operation.</p>



<p>“While we’re excited about how far we’ve come, this is only the beginning,” concluded Dominato. “As we get closer to election day, we will be ramping up our door-knocking with the goal of connecting with every single household in the City.”</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver is the only party in the Vancouver municipal elections running to win majorities on Council, Park Board, and School Board.</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver has nominated nineteen candidates for the October 15th municipal elections; Ken Sim for Mayor; Lenny Zhou, Peter Meiszner, Brian Montague, Mike Klassen, and incumbent City Councillors Rebecca Bligh, Lisa Dominato, and Sarah Kirby-Yung for Council; Brennan Bastyovanszky, Laura Christensen, Angela Haer, Marie-Claire Howard, Scott Jensen, and Jas Virdi for Park Board; Alfred Chien, Preeti Faridkot, Victoria Jung, Christopher Richardson, and Josh Zhang for School Board.</p>



<p>-30-</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong></p>



<p>Taylor Verrall</p>



<p>604-968-3067 | <a href="mailto:taylor@abcvancouver.ca">taylor@abcvancouver.ca<br><br></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/abc-vancouver-hits-two-substantial-campaign-milestones/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ABC Vancouver announces plans to address misogyny, homophobia, and sexual violence in sport through groundbreaking ‘safe sport officer’ program</title>
		<link>/abc-vancouver-announces-plans-to-address-misogyny-homophobia-and-sexual-violence-in-sport-through-groundbreaking-safe-sport-officer-program/</link>
					<comments>/abc-vancouver-announces-plans-to-address-misogyny-homophobia-and-sexual-violence-in-sport-through-groundbreaking-safe-sport-officer-program/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Team Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 15:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9057</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE September 20, 2022 VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC majority on Park Board would initiate a groundbreaking voluntary ‘safe sport officer’ program to help promote safety and inclusivity within sports organizations that use Park Board fields and facilities. “This is a groundbreaking policy and an opportunity for Vancouver to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE</p>



<p>September 20, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC majority on Park Board would initiate a groundbreaking voluntary ‘safe sport officer’ program to help promote safety and inclusivity within sports organizations that use Park Board fields and facilities.<br></p>



<p>“This is a groundbreaking policy and an opportunity for Vancouver to show national leadership,” said Brennan Bastyovanszky, ABC Park Board candidate and founder of the Vancouver Rogues Gay and Inclusive Rugby Club. “Today’s commitment is a major step in the right direction towards addressing issues around safety and inclusion.”</p>



<p>Systemic challenges regarding misogyny, homophobia, and sexual violence have been brought to the forefront by stories involving amateur, professional, and international sports organizations, The voluntary program would make safe sport officers available as an accessible resource to sports leagues, teams, and clubs that utilize Park Board-managed fields, parks, and facilities.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“In light of recent international scandals, such as the ones affecting Hockey Canada and USA Gymnastics, we feel that Park Board has a responsibility to do what we can to promote a tolerant and welcoming culture,” continued Bastyovanszky. “To address deep-rooted challenges of misogyny, homophobia, and sexual violence, we need to ensure that all those who use Park Board facilities feel safe and welcomed.”</p>



<p>Safe sport officers will be able to provide independent oversight of league or club operations in addition to providing resources such as equity, diversity, and inclusivity training or assistance in the development of inclusivity-positive policies within organizations. Following examples of similar programs in Australia and the Netherlands, the safe sport officer program in Vancouver would be among the first of its kind in Canada.</p>



<p>“It’s one thing to talk about making our City a more inclusive, welcoming, and safe place,” concluded Bastyovanszky. “An ABC-led Park Board will commit resources towards making that a reality.”</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver is the only party in the Vancouver municipal elections running to win majorities on Council, Park Board, and School Board.</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver has nominated nineteen candidates for the October 15th municipal elections; Ken Sim for Mayor; Lenny Zhou, Peter Meiszner, Brian Montague, Mike Klassen, and incumbent City Councillors Rebecca Bligh, Lisa Dominato, and Sarah Kirby-Yung for Council; Brennan Bastyovanszky, Laura Christensen, Angela Haer, Marie-Claire Howard, Scott Jensen, and Jas Virdi for Park Board; Alfred Chien, Preeti Faridkot, Victoria Jung, Christopher Richardson, and Josh Zhang for School Board.<br></p>



<p>-30-</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong></p>



<p>Taylor Verrall</p>



<p>604-968-3067 | <a href="mailto:taylor@abcvancouver.ca">taylor@abcvancouver.ca<br><br></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/abc-vancouver-announces-plans-to-address-misogyny-homophobia-and-sexual-violence-in-sport-through-groundbreaking-safe-sport-officer-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ABC Vancouver announce plan to deliver 5,000 new childcare spaces</title>
		<link>/abc-vancouver-announce-plan-to-deliver-5000-new-childcare-spaces/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Team Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 22:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE September 15, 2022 VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC majority on Council would deliver 5,000 new childcare spaces over the first four years of an ABC-led City Hall. “Today’s announcement to deliver 5,000 new childcare spaces will offer much-needed support for parents across Vancouver,” said ABC Councillor Lisa Dominato. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE</p>



<p>September 15, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC majority on Council would deliver 5,000 new childcare spaces over the first four years of an ABC-led City Hall.</p>



<p>“Today’s announcement to deliver 5,000 new childcare spaces will offer much-needed support for parents across Vancouver,” said ABC Councillor Lisa Dominato. “This plan we’re announcing today uses every tool at Council’s disposal to support and encourage the creation of a significant number of new childcare spaces.”</p>



<p>The ABC childcare plan includes pledges to harmonize childcare policy between municipal and Provincial governments, help childcare providers become compliant through the licensing process, make additional city land available for childcare facilities, and direct permit fees toward creating new spaces.</p>



<p>“At a time when many families across Vancouver are struggling to make ends meet, it’s important that we are focused on helping make life easier,” continued Dominato. “An investment in quality childcare is an investment in children, families, and the local economy.”</p>



<p>According to the Vancouver Sun, the City of Vancouver is currently facing a 17,000 childcare space shortfall.</p>



<p>“It’s important that we have enough childcare spaces to keep pace with the growing needs of families in our city,” continued Dominato. “Finding quality childcare is often one of the biggest and most stressful task families face; an ABC-led City Hall will work with the Provincial and Federal government to make this easier and secure additional resources.”</p>



<p>The plan also includes a commitment to work with an ABC majority on School Board to ensure that newly constructed schools in the City of Vancouver accommodate childcare facilities.</p>



<p>“Our city needs leadership that is focused on bringing people together to address the issues we see today,” concluded Dominato. “A collaborative approach will ensure that we can make meaningful progress on childcare.”</p>



<p>ABC Councillors met with the Minister of State for Childcare earlier this week at the Union of British Columbia Municipalities convention.</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver has nominated nineteen candidates for the October 15th municipal elections; Ken Sim for Mayor; Lenny Zhou, Peter Meiszner, Brian Montague, Mike Klassen, and incumbent City Councillors Rebecca Bligh, Lisa Dominato, and Sarah Kirby-Yung for Council; Brennan Bastyovanszky, Laura Christensen, Angela Haer, Marie-Claire Howard, Scott Jensen, and Jas Virdi for Park Board; Alfred Chien, Preeti Faridkot, Victoria Jung, Christopher Richardson, and Josh Zhang for School Board.</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver is the only party in the Vancouver municipal elections running to win majorities on Council, Park Board, and School Board.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">-30-</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong></p>



<p>Taylor Verrall<br><a href="mailto:taylor@abcvancouver.ca" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">taylor@abcvancouver.ca</a> | 604-968-3067</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Statement from Ken Sim in response to Kennedy Stewart’s misleading news release</title>
		<link>/statement-from-ken-sim-in-response-to-kennedy-stewarts-misleading-news-release/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Team Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 21:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9048</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE September 15, 2022 VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver mayoral candidate Ken Sim released the following statement in response to Mayor Kennedy Stewart’s misleading statement regarding the road tax: “ABC has been continuously running radio ads about the Mayor’s record on the road tax since the start of our advertising campaign. “The Mayor’s voting [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE</p>



<p>September 15, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver mayoral candidate Ken Sim released the following statement in response to Mayor Kennedy Stewart’s misleading statement regarding the road tax:</p>



<p>“ABC has been continuously running radio ads about the Mayor’s record on the road tax since the start of our advertising campaign.</p>



<p>“The Mayor’s voting history on the road tax is on the public record. Under his watch, $1.5 Million was spent on staff, consultancy firms, and stakeholder engagement related to the development of a road tax. Kennedy Stewart’s implausible denials cannot be trusted.</p>



<p>“It’s no surprise that Kennedy Stewart is once again attempting to deflect away from negative coverage of his campaign.</p>



<p>“Just this week, he was blasted multiple times for his disastrous record on housing and public safety, and most recently, a senior staff member in the Mayor’s office has been accused of ethical violations relating to a dropped list of what appear to be fundraisers for Kennedy Stewart’s Forward Together party.</p>



<p>“ABC will not be intimidated by Kennedy Stewart’s attempt to change the channel away from his failings as Mayor and we will not stop holding him accountable for his record on the road tax.”</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">-30-</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong></p>



<p>Taylor Verrall<br><a href="mailto:taylor@abcvancouver.ca" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">taylor@abcvancouver.ca</a> | 604-968-3067</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Statement from Ken Sim on the release of Kennedy Stewart’s housing platform</title>
		<link>/statement-from-ken-sim-on-the-release-of-kennedy-stewarts-housing-platform/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Team Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 18:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASESeptember 13, 2022 VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver mayoral candidate Ken Sim released the following statement in response to the announcement of Kennedy Stewart’s housing platform: “Kennedy Stewart has been Mayor for the last four years. His housing record speaks for itself. “During Kennedy Stewart’s term as Mayor, housing prices have gone up by [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE<br>September 13, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver mayoral candidate Ken Sim released the following statement in response to the announcement of Kennedy Stewart’s housing platform:</p>



<p>“Kennedy Stewart has been Mayor for the last four years. His housing record speaks for itself.</p>



<p>“During Kennedy Stewart’s term as Mayor, <a href="https://www.rebgv.org/content/rebgv-org/market-watch/MLS-HPI-home-price-comparison.html">housing prices</a> have gone up by 18% on the West side of Vancouver and by 28% on the East side of Vancouver. In the last two years alone, <a href="http://source/">average rents</a> city-wide have increased by 30%. Things have gotten so bad that David Eby is <a href="https://www.westerninvestor.com/british-columbia/province-steps-in-to-advance-bc-housing-starts-5292136">considering legislation</a> to force the Mayor’s hand on increasing supply.</p>



<p>“When it comes to social and supportive housing, Kennedy has encouraged an environment of quantity over quality. What’s being offered today in supportive housing is woefully inadequate. Inside an SRO, it can get up to over 40 degrees in the Summer, leading to a seasonal increase in the number of tents in our city.</p>



<p>“In the City of Vancouver, it takes longer for a high-rise apartment building to get built than it did to fight and win in World War II. In the midst of a housing crisis, that’s absolutely unacceptable.</p>



<p>“Kennedy Stewart’s inaction on housing has directly led to the situation we see today — an unaffordable city where younger generations are unable to see a future for themselves and the most vulnerable do not have access to adequate housing.</p>



<p>“We can improve the quality of supportive housing units, we can deliver high-rises within a year, we can double the number of co-ops in the city — we can make meaningful progress on housing but that’s only possible with an ABC majority on Council.”</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver will be releasing its 40+ point housing plan shortly.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">-30-</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Taylor Verrall<br>604-968-3067 | <a href="mailto:taylor@abcvancouver.ca" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">taylor@abcvancouver.ca</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ABC Vancouver commits to restoring honours programs and the School Liaison Officer program</title>
		<link>/abc-vancouver-commits-to-restoring-honours-programs-and-the-school-liaison-officer-program/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Team Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 16:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcvancouver.ca/?p=9035</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASESeptember 13, 2022 VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC majority on School Board would restore honours programs in Vancouver schools and reinstate the School Liaison Officer program. “Today, ABC Vancouver is excited to announce the first two major pieces of our school board platform,” said ABC School Board candidate Preeti [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE<br>September 13, 2022</p>



<p>VANCOUVER — ABC Vancouver announced today that an ABC majority on School Board would restore honours programs in Vancouver schools and reinstate the School Liaison Officer program.</p>



<p>“Today, ABC Vancouver is excited to announce the first two major pieces of our school board platform,” said ABC School Board candidate Preeti Faridkot. “These two policies will signal a major shift in direction for the Vancouver School Board.”</p>



<p>In 2021, the Vancouver School Board announced that honours programs would be cut. ABC’s primary focus of the School Board campaign is to promote and advance a greater amount of individualized learning opportunities.</p>



<p>“Our children are all different. We should be pursuing policies that promote more individuality, not less,” said ABC School Board candidate Josh Zhang. “Restoring honours programs will help the VSB provide world-class education.”</p>



<p>Amidst Vancouver’s public safety crisis, an ABC majority on School Board will also reinstate an updated version of the School Liaison Officer program, an initiative also cut in 2021 by the existing members of the School Board.</p>



<p>“A return of the School Liaison Officer program is something that many students, parents, and educators have been calling for,” concluded Faridkot. “Reinstating an updated version of the program will be an excellent step towards creating safer, more welcoming schools while addressing concerns that led to the program being cut in the first place.”</p>



<p>ABC Vancouver has nominated nineteen candidates for the October 15th municipal elections; Ken Sim for Mayor; Lenny Zhou, Peter Meiszner, Brian Montague, Mike Klassen, and incumbent City Councillors Rebecca Bligh, Lisa Dominato, and Sarah Kirby-Yung for Council; Brennan Bastyovanszky, Laura Christensen, Angela Haer, Marie-Claire Howard, Scott Jensen, and Jas Virdi for Park Board; Alfred Chien, Preeti Faridkot, Victoria Jung, Christopher Richardson, and Josh Zhang for School Board.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">-30-</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Taylor Verrall<br>604-968-3067 | <a href="mailto:taylor@abcvancouver.ca" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">taylor@abcvancouver.ca</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
